[{"answer": "What's our deal", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "How lucky's Miss Universe gotta be", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "This I gotta see...  ...the", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I have faith.  In horoscopes and fortune cookies..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Lemon doesn't go in Gin and Tonics, my friend'.  Where ya' from", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You in that place workin' on your complexion...", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What happened to the last transporter you ", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Do we need this...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Like...", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No.  You gonna give me phony reassurances", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "\"Extra", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He tried to..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I do.  We don't do business with him..", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'll be there", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "The Keys", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "that place?  Cubans don't like us or my business..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "My cousin is the harbor master. You must not bring in drugs.  You cannot be armed.  If you're carrying, it has to go.  Or stow it inside.  No one will go near your boat..", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I never do business in that place.  And nobody goes to that place but me.  And he is not my husband..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Verdado where", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "that place, that place...", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's in the suburbs outside that place", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No.  that place, that place.  Don't we have a meet", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "We're makin' moves on each other", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Then that's it.  Change the mission statement. my friend stays in.  He keeps working up the ladder.  The local importers get a pass for the time being", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes you do..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "There is", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I am asking.  You to me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You think I am in so deep I forgot", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Do you ...I have forgotten I am a cop", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " All I want to know is the where and the when.  Spare me mini moves, progress reports and bullshit", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I got the item", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " 2", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Make it 35", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "  Yeah", "docId": "miami-vice.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Where's the new drop point...", "qsentId": 36}]